washingtontechnology.org 2014-05-14

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 13, 2013.

Welcome to washingtontechnology.org (“Site“), which is owned by and operated by Washington Technology Industry Association, a 501 (c) 6 not-for-profit corporation, and its corporate affiliates (collectively, “us“, “we”, “our”, or “WTIA“). This privacy policy explains our data collection, use, and disclosure practices with respect to information collected on the Site. If you have questions about these practices, please contact us by email at support@washingtontechnology.org {??}

**1\. Information Collected**

When you register for an account on the Site, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your email address and your professional skills. Also, we may offer the ability to connect to Third-Party Connected Services (as defined below in the “Third-Party Connected Services” section of this Policy) during the registration process, either to register for our Site or to link a Third-Party Connected Service to your account on the Site. We collect personal information from those Third-Party Connected Services as described below in that section.

Additionally, when you use the Site, we collect additional personal information when you engage in activities such as setting up your personal profile, making connections with other users, sending messages, performing searches and queries, enrolling in events and courses, and transmitting information through various channels. We retain such information indefinitely. When you update personal information, we may keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

You can choose not to provide certain personal information to us, but some basic information about your skills and goals are required in order for you to register and participate in the features offered through the Site.

We may automatically collect some information about your computer or other device when you visit the Site. Such automatically-collected information includes, for example, your IP address, Web browser software (e.g., Google Chrome or Internet Explorer), and the referring web site. We also may collect information about your activity on this Site, such as the events in which you enroll. One of our goals in collecting this automatic information is to help improve your user experience.

We may collect this information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). If we link or associate any information gathered through passive means with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information under this privacy policy. Otherwise, we use and disclose information collected by passive means in aggregate form or otherwise in a non-personally identifiable form. We may use and disclose information that has been aggregated or otherwise is not personally identifiable to third parties for various purposes.

We also may receive information about you, including personal information, from third parties, and may combine this information with other personal information we maintain about you that we collect on the Site. If we do so, this privacy policy governs any combined information that we maintain in personally identifiable format.

**2\. Use of Personal Information**

We will use personal information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to respond to your questions and comments; to communicate with you via regular mail and email (or other electronic means) about our programs and services; to personalize content on the Site; to measure interest in, and to administer and improve, our services and Site, and to develop new features, functionality, products, and services; to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems; to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users; to prevent potentially illegal activities; and to enforce our Terms of Service.

We may also use personal information for any other purposes that we may disclose to you in connection with a request for your personal information, and for any other use for which you may provide your consent.

Please review “Your choices with respect to the Collection and Use of Personal Information” below.

**3\. Disclosure of Personal Information**

We display some of your profile information (minus your email address and password) to other registered and unregistered users of the Site, including people browsing for connections on the Site, and to support other Site functions. We also may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:

(a) To third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, such as customer service, business analytics, marketing, and services to us in connection with operating the Site. These vendors have access to personal information needed to perform their functions and we require them to agree not to share or use the information for any other purpose.

(b) To business partners with whom we may jointly offer an education product (e.g. leadership best practices, agile development methodology, etc.) or a service offering (e.g. mobile application webinar, leadership training classes, etc.). Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners, but we will make reasonable effort to ensure they protect your privacy.

(c) When we deem it advisable or necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements.

(d) As necessary, in our sole discretion, to protect the perceived rights, safety and property of users of the Site, and the public.

(e) In connection with a change of control or operations, including without limitation in any merger, acquisition, reorganization, restructuring or any other transfer of all or substantially all of our assets, or a transfer of the operations of the Site.

(f) If you have access to premium content on the Site via a WTIA enterprise subscription agreement between WTIA and your employer or another entity, you hereby permit WTIA to provide reports regarding your usage of the services on the Site, including personal information, to the subscribing entity during the term of that enterprise subscription.

Other than as set out above and for any other disclosures for which you provide your consent, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

Also, as an example of the uses and disclosures that we may make of information that has been aggregated or otherwise is anonymous, we may share such information with third parties, including sponsors and other non-profit associations. For example, we may tell a sponsor the number of visitors to the Site.

**4\. A Special Word about Communications Channels and Profile Information**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on areas of our Site that are accessible by third parties (including users of the Site and others), such as user profiles or information that you share through communications channels available on the Site, that information can be collected and used by others. By posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. We may make available from time to time options for keeping certain user profile information private, but we cannot guarantee that third parties will not gain access to any such information.

**5\. Access to Personal Information**

You may access and update many categories of personal information we maintain about you by updating your profile information while logged in to the Site. You may request that WTIA update or make changes to personal information that we have collected on the Site by sending an email to support@washingtontechnology.org {??} We may require a user who seeks to make updates or changes to personal information to take steps to allow us to verify his or her identity.

**6\. Your Choices With Respect to the Collection and Use of Personal Information**

(a) As noted above, you can choose not to provide us with personal information, although it may be needed to register as a member on the Site and to participate in certain features offered through the Site.

(b) You may stop the delivery of email communications by making the appropriate election while logged into the Site, following the instructions accompanying a particular communication, or by contacting us at support@washingtontechnolog.org {??}

**7\. Security**

While no web site can guarantee security, we have implemented administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect personal information in our control. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions.

**8\. Children Under 13**

The Site may only be used by children under 13 with the written authorization provided by the school or other educational organization registering the child. We do not permit self-registration by children under 13. We do not authorize disclosure of personally identifiable information by any child under 13. If you believe that any personally identifiable information from or about a child under 13 is displayed in a member profile on the Site, please contact us at support@washingtontechnolog.org {??}. We will immediately investigate and delete any personally identifiable information about a child under 13 and inform the school or educational organization of the change.

**9\. Third Party Websites and Services**

Web sites and services to which this Site links do not operate under this privacy policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other web sites and services to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**10\. Third Party Connected Services**

We may from time to time permit users with accounts on certain third-party services such as Facebook (“Third-Party Connected Services”) to log in to such third-party services through the Site, and may offer you the ability to connect to Third-Party Connected Services on the Site. For example, we may allow you to register for our Site through use of a Third-Party Connected Service. If you connect to any of our Services through a Third-Party Connected Service, you may be able to send alerts, comments, and messages on such third-party services, and may publish some of your activities on our Site to the third-party service. In any request for authorization to connect, we may ask you for additional rights or permissions with respect to Third-Party Connected Services and information, including personal information, which we obtain from them.

Any personal information you provide on or to any Third-Party Connected Service is provided directly to such Third-Party Connected Service and is subject to that third party’s policies governing privacy and security. We are not responsible for the sharing, posting, commenting, or other content and information-gathering practices on any Third-Party Connected Services. Please review their terms of service and privacy policies carefully before using any Third-Party Connected Services and connecting to our Services.

By connecting to any Third-Party Connected Services in connection with our Site, you permit us to access and use all information related to your account on the Third-Party Connected Service that may be accessible to us through the any Third-Party Connected Service pursuant to this Policy. For example, if you permit us to connect to your Facebook profile, we may collect information from your Facebook profile such as your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you’ve made public. To limit or control the information that is available to us through any such Third-Party Connected Service, or to disconnect any Third-Party Connected Service from our Site, you should check (and, if applicable, modify) the applicable settings on the Third-Party Connected Service.

**11\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy in the future to reflect changes in our privacy practices, our website functionality, or applicable legislation, so please check back often. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on the Site.

**12\. How You Can Contact Us**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, email us at support@washingtontechnolog.org {??}, or write to us at:

WTIA – Privacy Officer  
2200 Alaskan Way  
Suite #390  
Seattle WA 98121
